Thank you for watching!
Mn.
Ohhhhhhhh!
It's the morning chime, and we're about to start the daytime show.
I was thinking that I'd like to be a part of this, so I did it, and then I tried it.
I thought, "Is she looking a bit nubby?" I don't see any flowers today.
I'm not sure if it's because I don't have any flowers, but I don't have any flowers today.
I'm just trying to relax and take it easy.
I'd like to start with today's mc before we begin.
I'd like to start with today's topic before we start the program.
Dat musste h in America in the inside of the Fujita Kahoichi Achi wa chuische sekai sha
same frame till shampoo point out to me so I shuffle it around and everyone is on 1
Poof!
I'm sorry, but I'm going to have to ask you all to vote or vote for me.
I thought you ladies would like to start, okay, so let's get started.
I've been going to the Queen's for about a year now.
I've been there since November... but it's been a while since we've been together.
I'm sure... after all... we'd like to finish. 54... come on...
No, it's not.
I'm going to get a mouth pick.
8-week wedding kick!
Okay...
I'm sure you've already announced the results of the ceremony... 50.9 percent for one and 49.1 percent for two... so that makes one...
I'll give you the "one"...
I'll play...
I'll play the game.
I'll be in charge of today's session, and I'll be in charge of today's session, and I'll be in charge of today's session.
I'll get started.
Yeah... yeah...
Thank you for watching the 66th edition of Ebichu Fun and Humhumhum Showroom today.
I'd like to take a moment to spread the word about this showroom.
In order for as many people as possible to see it, we're going to announce it on the official Ebichu x page, so please spread the word!
composite
Thank you very much!
I'm sure it's hard to watch the video at this time of the day.
I'm sure it's hard to watch the show at this time of night, right?
It depends on the person, but if you're a student or something, you're probably already under the covers, just before you go to sleep, so you can watch it while relaxing.
I'm not going to let you sleep. I'm not going to let you sleep.
I'm not going to let you sleep.
I'd like to go on to the next one.
I'm going to take a survey before I post my talk, so that I can decide what to talk about.
I'll show you the questionnaire.
We've got themes 1 through 7 like this.
First of all, the city of Indigo Hour, here we are on February 28th of this year.
Hey, Indigo Hour, this is us on February 28th of the year Indigo Hour, this is us on February 28th of the year
Three Prices Eight Guards Three Prices Eight Leis
That's the title of the album, yes, but it's up to all of you to decide whether or not you agree with me that we're winning.
You don't seem to understand, do you?
I'm always short of money next to DN.
I'm sure it's the endless art experience uns Neko Re ii Ah q times more!
I've noticed a lot of progress lately.
I'm sure you're right!
I'd like to present a show called "7 Showrooms" with these 7 pieces.
What you will hear depends on you!
It's up to all of you!
What would you like to hear first?
Let's have a vote.
Let the voting begin!
Let's get started.
All of you!
What is it?
I think it's obvious at first.
What's the number?
Well...
Well, you know...
I've watched a lot of TV programs.
I think there are a lot of people here who are used to it.
Of course.
What do you think, guys?
We don't tolerate betrayal.
We're very strict.
My sister...
She's very strict.
She's very strict. It's tough.
All right, then.
Four.
The end.
We're not very good at countdowns, are we?
Weak.
I guess we're weak on numbers.
Ben
I'm surprised.
Seven.
I'm going to start with a seven.
I thought I was going to start with 7
From a subtle number.
Okay, what was number one?
I'd like to know what came in first, please.
Yes, ma'am.
So...
Number one.
Thank you very much.
You're all so kind.
I mean kind.
About the Indigo Hour.
I'd like to talk to you about Indigo Hour.
Yes, ma'am.
This is it.
It will be released on February 28th.
It's an album.
Yes.
First of all...
Yesterday, right after yesterday.
Yesterday.
Tinkle.
Tinkle wink.
Tinkle wink
Tinkle Wink
Music video for "Tinkle Wink" was released and stuff. The music video of the "I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry" was released and so on.
Yes.
It's going viral.
Have you seen it?
The music video
Did you see it?
The music video was great.
Thank you!
It's great.
I don't know.
Yeah, it's...
It's like I can hang on to it a little bit.
You can.
Yeah.
A song.
Here.
Okay, well, I'll just...
Hey, Tinkle Wink, I want you guys to hear this.
Hey.
I'll see if I can find it.
Okay, let's see.
Let the music begin!
Crying and laughing
Oh!
Nonaka-san starts that part.
It's high from the door ball, isn't it?
This song is so high!
It's so high.
I don't know, it's so high.
I don't know...
Let's all try it out once.
If it's too high, we'll lower the key a little.
We discussed whether or not to lower the key a little if it was too high.
So we decided to give it a try.
I don't know...
The first part of the song has already finished playing.
There's a part in the beginning where the chorus says, "This moment, this moment...
I heard there was a debate over whether it was me or Mirei. I heard there was a dispute over whether it was me or Mirei over there.
Oh, I see.
So it's already too high, too high key.
The highest part of the key...
It didn't sound like me.
Speaking of high notes, you're Mirei, right?
That's for sure.
That's what she was thinking.
I thought the music video might have helped everyone inquire a little bit.
What do you think?
By the way, the trilogy that is the heart of this indigarber
Yes.
The trilogy by Chiaki Sato.
Blue Dignity, Crystal Drop and Tinkle Wink.
They came out one after the other.
Yes.
It's kind of nice, isn't it?
It's nice. It's like a cute girl is the main character.
It's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like...
It's a really easy-to-understand coming-of-age story.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can feel the coming-of-age through the whole piece.
I think it's great that you can feel youth through the whole trilogy, and even if you just take out the trilogy, you can still feel youth.
Is there anything you want to say? What do you want to ask about the album?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Any comments?
If you like.
I'd love to hear from you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, and the outfit was cute.
Thank you.
It's adorable.
It's a black-and-white ribbon-based costume for this album's visuals.
It's a little bit classical chic, an atmosphere we haven't had in a while.
It's not like we're saying this ourselves, but...
It finally has a private feel to it.
We're finally getting that "private" feeling. You're finally getting that private feeling.
I sure would like to be told that.
Like she's a nice young lady.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, the Blue Dignity outfit, too.
It's a little bit like... what was it? Like tennis wear.
Yeah, yeah.
It was kind of classy.
That's right.
Well, you know, things changed as the temple grew.
Yes.
From the private school to the public school...
Yes, yes.
Uniformity or something like that.
Yeah, yeah...
It's starting to become a normal private school.
That's true.
It was loose at high speed.
It was loose.
But I don't know...
Yeah.
It's got a private school feel.
It's coming out.
I think it's cute.
Oh, how was the music video shooting?
The music video shoot focused mainly on dance this time.
That's right.
It was a music video that challenged me a lot in terms of dance.
The choreography was a bit choreographed, with a lot of hand gestures and stuff.
Yes.
It was a little difficult to remember.
It was difficult.
We all taught each other and tried our best.
And we said, "OK!
We announced it.
Yes, I did.
But, you know, I don't think I've ever shot so many music videos in such a short period of time. But, you know, I don't think I've ever shot so many music videos in such a short period of time.
That's for sure... Oh, yeah, you've got a trilogy of music videos out now, right?
Yes, and all of them were very dramatic, which is something we haven't seen in the past.
Yes, there have been a lot of that recently.
But it's different from that, it's a new kind of music video.
Yes, that's right.
Dancing and expressing each other's facial expressions.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like an idol music video.
That's right.
Epitude is pretty rare, isn't it?
It's rare.
It's like a little bit of blue dizziness, and the sound of the samaguri...
Yeah.
There are some parts in the music video that link to each other.
Yeah...
There are also some parts of the choreography that link to the music video.
That's right.
That's the point of this trilogy.
I want you to find it.
Yes, I do.
Album.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
There's a lot more variety on the album than just those three songs.
That's good.
Yeah, they've been released on radio stations all over the place.
That's right.
Please look forward to the release of the album!
I'm looking forward to it!
Okay then.
Okay...
Let's talk about this.
It's good. Great.
I think we're done here for now.
It was nice talking to you.
Good.
Thank you very much.
We'll get right to it.
Okay.
Okay, well, this one's already done.
Of the two through seven...
I wonder what he wants to hear.
I'm sure you do.
Well, the first time we did it... it was pretty close all the way around, except for that one.
I think they were about the same.
I mean, to be honest, I don't even know how to write this, so it's not like any of them make much difference.
I don't know who wrote which one.
It's not like the headline says, "I'm really interested in this.
Because, you know...
There's a big difference, too.
Yeah.
So, how about it, everybody?
I'd like to call for the next theme.
Let's begin.
Here we go.
What's going on? What's going on?
What is it? -Hey, listen to this.
Listen to the episode we've come up with. We'll probably have more than usual.
Yes, we're pretty confident about the questionnaire.
Yes, we are. We're especially confident.
Yes, we are.
Five-four-four-three-two.
I'm in a hurry to say 5-4-3-2-5-4-3-2-5-4-3-2-5-4-3-2-5-4-3-2
It's hard to count.
Is that okay?
Since you just said 5-4-3, what's the next talk?
Next talk is number two!
Number 2! Number 2!
And by number two, I mean money is always short.
Well, that's certainly a headline I'd be interested in.
What's this? That's me.
Yes, it's me.
Maybe you've heard this somewhere in your sister's talk.
I had dinner with Emayuna once.
That's nice.
Was it the first time the three of us went out for dinner together?
Of course, I'm her senior.
That's right.
You're both still minors. You're both students.
There's a 10-year age difference.
So I bought them dinner.
Oh!
I paid for both of them.
That's right.
So we had a nice dinner, and I told him we had a good time.
And then...
And then we both got on the train... and it was late... and... we had dinner at night, so...
I was worried about them, so I said, "Let's take the train home together.
And the three of us headed for the ticket gate...
And then...
And then I popped in my watermelon and they both popped out.
All right.
And they went in.
So gentle.
I thought, "Oh, he's in." I thought, "Oh, he's in.
I thought, "Well, I'll go in too," and I blew on it.
I found only 20 yen in that watermelon.
How little!
And Yuna was messing with it somewhere.
Aya was so cool to treat him like that, but there was only 20 yen in the watermelon.
That's not cool.
Yeah, not cool.
I heard you say that somewhere.
That's so uncool
I wasn't embarrassed by the 20 yen either. I wasn't ashamed of that twenty either.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm always living on the edge, so I thought it was nothing.
But when I heard that you talked about it on the radio, I thought it was a little embarrassing to have only 20 yen in my pocket.
That's right.
So, while I was having this episode, I decided to go on a little trip with a friend of mine.
We had some time to kill, so we took the bus to a place deep in Chiba, which takes a couple of hours to get there, but the bus was leaving in about 5 minutes, and we had to run a little bit before the bus time.
I had to run to get on the bus.
I said I wanted to stop at a convenience store and have a cup of coffee on the bus.
Ah...
So I said, "Let's stop at the convenience store" and he said, "Wow!
And then I said, "Well, my friends are pretty messy, so I want to do something like this, so when I was a kid, there was a lot of that going on.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Many of my friends are quite caring, so when we go to the convenience store, I say, "Well, I'll buy one for Ai-chan too! Like that.
That's very kind.
I felt sorry for them, so I told them to let me pay for it this time.
So, as usual, I used my watermelon to conveniently buy a coffee, so I hurriedly chose a coffee with only 5 minutes to go, and when I peeled it off, there was only 20 yen in it.
I was in such a hurry that I couldn't help but say, "I only have 20 yen in my pocket. I said, "Money!
I made him pay by putting the money in the bus. I made him pay.
I was so embarrassed.
Money!
It wasn't that I was short of money or anything.
It was just that moment when I couldn't use it anymore.
I was in a hurry, so I said, "Money! I was in a hurry, so I said, "Money!
I was so embarrassed.
That's why I'm always short of money.
I'm called the 20-yen girl.
A 20-yen woman.
I wonder why. I always put an extra 10,000 yen or so in my pocket, but the next thing I know, it's just 20 yen.
That's strange.
It's strange. It's not that I've been working during the daytime for years and have to make a living on a shoestring budget.
It's not that I'm living on a shoestring.
I should be getting enough money to enjoy my life.
I want to pay the train fare.
I want to pay it, don't you? I'm working so hard.
I want to pay it, but it's always short.
Also, I thought that you can't use your mind at the last minute.
You call me a mother. That's true. You've been called a mother. That's true.
That's true. That's funny. Let's see...
She was a 20-yen woman.
Thank you very much.
See? We're having an episode, right?
That's right.
I've been thinking about it.
It's so bad that Yuni is messing with me.
I feel like she's watching me. It's a little embarrassing.
It's like Yuna's not behind me.
She's watching me.
It's really embarrassing, isn't it?
I see.
It was embarrassing.
She was such a nice 20-yen woman.
Let's move on to the next part of the talk.
What would you like next?
What would you like?
How about after 3, now that we have finished 12?
I'm sure you're easy to tease.
I thought she was cute... for someone so many years younger.
She didn't think I was cute because I didn't have money.
That might be hard. Count to five.
Four, three, two, one.
Finished.
And now, let's see what our next topic will be.
Next up, number five to Balenteren.
Two of them are a little timely, so let's see what you've got here.
Let me tell you something... this is me... Valentine's Day... well, it's more about the two of us, I guess.
I'm talking about me, or rather, the two of us... well, yes...
I'm sure you had a Valentine's Day... on the 14th... at the store.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a valentine for me...
You know, you did a radio interview with me... about Valentine's Day.
We were talking about exchanging valentines on the way to the Real Gamba on Valentine's Day.
But in the end, we had rehearsals for the fc that season, so we couldn't exchange food.
But we had rehearsals for the fc that season, so we were worried that we might catch a cold if we exchanged food.
We were worried that we might all catch a cold or something, so we decided to wait until after our important plans were over. I was worried about doing the exchange, so I decided to wait until after I had something important planned, and we ended up doing the exchange to do n p stand down to.
I couldn't do it properly.
But I felt a little bit of unresolved feelings about Valentine's Day.
I really wanted to make sweets for Valentine's Day.
That's great!
I made my own Valentine's Day just the day before yesterday.
That's nice.
So, the Valentine's Day candy I was planning to make was...
I was going to make a chocolate cake that was a little bit healthier.
I can make a little healthy chocolate cake.
Sounds delicious.
I thought I'd make it and eat it myself.
But that wasn't enough for me.
I had dinner with Kao-chan the day before.
She's a good cook.
I asked her if she had any suggestions for me. I asked him.
Tofu? He said you can make raw chocolate with tofu.
I can make it.
I thought that would be good, and it's healthy.
It's healthy.
And it's easy.
It's really easy.
You just melt the chocolate in a pot of boiling water.
And then you drain the tofu.
Smooth the tofu until there are no more grains.
Then mix in the chocolate and let it harden.
Yeah, that sounds really easy!
I thought for sure I could do it, even though I'm clumsy.
I went home, bought some tofu, and if there was chocolate, I bought some tofu.
I would make it like this at around midnight.
Here you go, consigme!
For seasoning.
How do you like it?
One by one.
It's very quick and easy.
Right?
And maybe
A little bit. hey!
just a little bit
A little bit.
I think I've had an effect on you.
I'm still working on it.
melts the tofu with the tofu with the sweetness i just put it in the tofu here
for 10 minutes
I just put it in the tofu here for 10 minutes and then I just put it in the chocolate and then I reincarnate it like me melts the tofu with the tofu with the sweetness.
I'm not convinced that I tried too hard to make it smooth, but I think it might be a bad idea from your point of view.
I mixed the chocolate and let it harden and then, well, as you can probably guess, it separated.
But then, as you can probably guess, it separated... and it didn't harden at all... and the heads weren't mixed in at all...
And then I thought that maybe I don't have a very good sense of humor, and that's why I'm telling you this story, only today.
I told the furniture about it the next day and they asked why I mixed it.
So I put the tofu in the deep dish and used a spoon, and I thought maybe I should give it a little bit of a stir to make it smoother.
I thought, "Well, I mixed it with a spoon, so I'll have to put it in my mom's." I thought, "Well, you'll have to start with the utensils, then.
You know, in the morning... in Kawada's opinion...
I guess she thought she had to have a bowl and a whisk to make the pastry in the first place.
So regardless of whether it's pastry or not, there's always a bowl and a whisk and a whipper in the house.
It's expected that every girl's house has one.
And I'm the kind of person who takes it for granted, so of course my mom thought she was mixing it with a spoon.
It's funny.
So I'm mixing it with a spoon as well, but it's not mixing.
I realized I needed a whisk.
Kao-chan looked so bashful.
She said, "That's where you started.
What? Time really did stop.
Time stopped.
That was before.
Well, I hadn't thought of that.
I didn't see that coming.
I've been downgrading my arsenal beyond the "Saaka-kata". You've been a minimalist this year.
But, well, if you're a man or someone who cooks at home, I'm sure there are people who use it just to save the eggs that are in the wrong place.
I've been doing everything with a spoon, so what's the hard mode from the halfway point?
I don't know if that's true, but it's true.
I saw a recipe for tofu that said it was easy to make.
That's right, that's right.
Some men say it's there, some say it's not.
Some say they don't. Some people say there isn't.
Some people say no.
Yeah.
Well, I guess girls do.
When you first start living on your own, you're gonna have everything you need.
When I cook, I use a plate and spoon for everything, so I don't have a mixer.
You don't have the concept of mixing, do you, Aiko? And you said you wash your dishes in hot water.
And I'm from there, too... and I'm from there... and East Live is talking about it.
When I first started living alone, I couldn't get rid of the grease, and even though I washed the dishes properly, the next day they were covered with a white curtain.
I wondered why, and the next day or the day after that, Mirei came to my house and washed the dishes for me.
I told her that she had to wash them with hot water and laugh at me because I drank hot water and told her to use oil.
So the curtain will be drawn on the day that Mirei will tell us that we'll be doing it with you.
I'm off for a bit... because the sky is empty... yes... that's right... she says she's doing it...
She's been doing that cooking show...
I'm learning a lot about life skills from you guys... so next time I buy this whipper and bowl... you'll make it for me... and next time I'll get the right equipment for it.
I'm sure you'll have a great time!
I'm thinking one more, one more, one more... what shall we do?
What shall we do?
But you know what, listen, there are two things I really want you to pick out for me and you.
I'd like you both to... come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on...
Well, well, well, well... since we're out, there's no Kabo episode.
It's okay. It's okay.
But guess which one? Five, four, three, two, one...
That's it.
Here are the results of the survey.
Number 6. What?
What? I liked number 4 recently.
I liked number 4 recently, but I'll talk about number 6.
Number 6 is my Sunday episode, but it's a little...
It may go back a long way, but it's something I'm not good at.
When I think about it, I'm not shy, but...
I'm not shy, but I'm not good with waitresses.
That's right, Kao-chan.
I don't like store clerks who come in with an eagerness to sell.
I see.
The moment you walk in, they say, "Welcome." "Please come in and take a look.
I feel like, "No, I'm here because I want to see your products.
I immediately feel sorry for the store clerks who work all over the country. I immediately feel sorry for all the clerks who work all over the country.
I'm not the type of person who's absolutely determined to make my sales.
I see.
When I go to a clothing store, I think, "This person is nice..." I walk in, see a mannequin wearing something nice, and I keep looking at it, and I think, "Oh, that's cute.
You can see her from a distance, and you can feel that a customer has arrived.
You can feel it, can't you?
She said, "Isn't that cute?
This sense of distance is very comfortable for someone who doesn't suddenly come over here.
That's still a long way off. I recommend it.
I'm still too far away.
I was told, "Oh, really?
I'm getting closer and closer to you.
I said, "You're tall, this would look good on you.
I said I'd buy it, and I did.
Like that.
Not all of a sudden.
I'm hoping that more and more people will start to get closer to me.
I'm hoping that more and more people will come to know me.
I see.
So, let's say...
Even if you want to be friends...
If you don't put a little cushion between you and them...
I can't get along with him.
I can't get along with them.
But I'm not a shy person. KahoYou are right, I am not shy. I can talk with everyone, but when I meet someone for the first time, I get surprised. I am surprised.
I put pictures of it in between. First of all, you want to see a picture of what kind of girl she is, before you play with her.
But that's not everyone.
Then you want to meet her, but you still want to have someone in between you and her.
Oh, not two people.
Let's have them come over for a bit.
Uh-huh.
And then we go.
Even when we went alone, it was only for a few hours.
Oh, we didn't get that deep into it.
And the next time, it was only half a day.
Isn't that how it is with friends? Friends.
That's why I wondered if he was shy at first. So once I thought for a minute that maybe I was shy.
I was like, "I don't know, can I call a friend?
I don't know, can I call my friend? I'm a stranger.
I'm a stranger.
So I said, "Yes,
What?
So it's like, you know, we'll just do it at a later date.
You need to be prepared.
Yeah.
Preparation is necessary.
I realized that recently. Oh, it's true, there are some things you can and can't do, like calling a friend of a friend to the emergency room.
I'm the type of person who is totally fine with it, so when someone says, "Well, let's call someone else," I'm like, "Okay, I'll do it. It's amazing, isn't it?
I'm like, "Oh, wow, that's great. I see. Then I guess store clerks would also prefer to be greeted by someone from Tokyo rather than suddenly saying, "Welcome!
From the Tokyo people
I'm sure that's scary, isn't it? I would be happy if I could start from that point.
You are strange. It really is. I can't tell you how many times I've been told that by an automated person.
I thought the waiter was really nice. Oh, I see. So she was the one who had a deep feeling for the place.
To be honest, I didn't like the whole outfit. I really liked this outfit that this mannequin was wearing.
I thought I might not buy much, but I've already made a loyalty card. Hahahaha, I'm easy. I'm easy. I was a surprisingly easy customer. That's right. I'm a bit of a tricky customer.
I wonder if my initial guard is hard. I see. I'm looking at it.
I just commented that I was watching them. At that moment, I would leave the restaurant. Oh, that's it. I see.
I see. I realized that. That's what I was talking about. It was something I noticed recently.
Let's go one more time. Let's do one more. Let's do one more. Okay, I've already decided.
Then it's already decided.
Okay. Guidance and support. Please choose number 4. This one, too.
How about it, everyone?
Yes, 54310.
That's fast. So we decided on number 4.
That's 88%. Everyone is so kind. We've decided on number 4. So far, we've talked a lot.
We talked about how we might not be shy, and we talked about how we might not be shy. I mentioned that I might not be shy, and that I had a lot of ideas for this kind of person.
This is a story about two people, isn't it? Yes, that's right. The other day. That's right.
We went to an art experience. To experience art. You know. I was the most interested in talking with him when he said he wanted to talk.
I thought, "Would you like to talk with me? So I went. I went to the art experience. Well, I would like you to take a look at the pictures today or tomorrow.
I hope you will see the pictures around here someday. I went to an art experience, and I painted on a round canvas.
I went to experience this kind of art experience, and I went to a place where you can make layers of paints on a round canvas, and then pour the paints on the canvas, and then turn the canvas around,
I went to experience it,
I was surprised to see so many couples around me. I was surprised to see so many couples around me. I thought, "Oh, yeah, that's right. It was the first time I knew that. It was the first time I went to such a place. I went to such a place for the first time, you know. So, you know, I whined. I was a little bit nervous.
I was working on it, but that session was over. When I was finished, I realized that the time frame for the art experience was set. Like, how many minutes to how many minutes. Yeah, yeah, yeah. But that session was over. When I was finished, I was told that the time frame for the art experience had been set, right? Like, how many minutes to how many minutes. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There was a person who came a little late. Yeah, yeah. And when he finished, he told everyone he was sorry for being late and came back.
There was a person whom I like to call "Gentle Gian.
There was a person called Gentle Gian. Yup.
When he said he was sorry, I thought that there was such a nice person, but there was also this "Gentle Giant,
First of all, he was wearing fluorescent orange sweatshirts.
I thought he was a nice guy.
He probably plays sports, right? He has a good body. He has great muscles. They were macho, and they were wearing them as a couple, and they looked macho, like this,
They were like, "We're going to do art! It was like, "This is how you do art! They were like, "Oh, my God, they look like that. They looked like they were going to bat or something,
I had an encounter, and the work was fluorescent orange. It was orange! I thought it was Gian, who loves fluorescent orange.
But there were so many people...
Who's there? I thought. It sure looked like the Gian from the movie, didn't it? Yes!
In terms of the degree of goodness. Yes, but, you know, they are hard to find in today's world. There are none. It's normal for people to say, "I'm sorry," when you are late, even if you are late for less than five minutes.
But after the meeting was over, he went out of his way to apologize to each and every one of us for being late today. But after the event, he went out of his way to apologize to each and every one of us for being late today, including these two. He said, "Oh, my God, that's so terrible.
He said, "It was fun, wasn't it? He was such a nice guy. He was a very nice person. But then I realized something.
There was that sister who was explaining to us, "Please do this." We were the only ones who were replying to each other, so it was cultivated during the day, after all.
And she said, "Come in," and we didn't even have to answer.
She said, "I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
She smiles every day, so when she says she's in, she smiles and says she's in, so it was a bit of a tense scene for her, but she seems to have loosened up.
She said it was a beautiful piece of work and the color was nice.
I'm glad. She didn't come all at once.
She came to me like she thought they were ready to go, so I asked her if she was okay, and she was like, "Excuse me, what's this?
He was a nice guy.
I told the girls I'd take their picture and they took it.
And they took a picture of the two of us together... in this position.
You know, like this, with your knees bent a little bit, and you're in a pose with your knees bent.
I saw somewhere that most Japanese people pose with their knees bent.
Every generation in that group.
When you go to China or Korea, for example, they pose with a car, or with a lotus, or with a lotus.
They pose a little more flamboyantly.
But Japanese people are like this.
They bend their knees.
That's why they do it naturally.
But he had a really nice smile.
That's for sure.
He's smiling like he's having fun, and he's sitting in the middle.
But he took the picture at an angle where he didn't have to be in the middle of the frame. But they took it at an angle of view that didn't require me to be in the middle of the frame.
There was so much horizontal frame.
but he went out of his way to make it look tiny in the big picture.
I'm talking about the fact that it made me smile again.
I wanted to talk about that.
I wanted to talk about the fact that I was relieved to see that the picture was so full of horizontal frames, but they went to the trouble of taking a large picture, and it turned out to be tiny.
I'm sorry I forced you to make it to 4, but I'm sorry...
Yeah...
I've done a lot so far, and I'm done, but next time...
My ending... my ending down... my ending inning ram.
I said I wanted to talk about it.
I'm sure each episode was long...
I'm sure after we'd eaten we'd never had such a long episode talk before.
That's true.
So, shall we wrap up the ending?
Can I make an announcement about the ending?
Yes, let's do it.
Yes, let me do that. I would like to make an announcement to everyone who has listened up to this point, so please listen to the announcement,
In February, on February 28th, our 8th album will be released, as I mentioned earlier.
Indigua Hour will be released on February 28.
Please look forward to it, and let's feel the youth of the world. Please come and enjoy it. Next, we are rehearsing to rave reviews.
Theater Shrimp 2020. Mystery!
Mystery! It's starting to be a mystery.
Sorry, I just couldn't resist. I'm sorry, I just couldn't resist.
Maybe you'll sneeze over here? Something on stage. It's not a stage. It doesn't matter when.
TheatreSyrimp2024 My Sweet Little Lucky.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, My Sweet Little Lucky will be at the Sunshine Theatre from March 9 to March 17, and I'm not sure if you'll be able to make it.
I'm sorry, but I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's amazing, isn't it?
As usual, as you may know from your visits to Theatre Shrimp...
I think you're right.
But it's just as well, isn't it?
I mean, the more I see Tsuchiya-san's songbook, the more I see it, the more I see it.
So no matter what time you come...
You can enjoy it no matter how many times you come.
You know, there are all kinds of tricks here and there.
You know, the more you look at it, the more you see the clues that lead up to the ending.
You're right. Yes, it is.
No way. It's full of surprises like this one here and this one here.
Really? You might be surprised.
I hope you'll come and find all the interesting points.
I'll be waiting for you.
Okay, bye.
Now that we're done, let's check out the final top 5 ranking.
4.
Thank you very much for the tea movie.
Thank you very much!
Thank you, Penrabunbun!
So, yes, this is a chat tb, or was it gpb that got you all today, and did it really make you feel like you don't belong?
First of all, let's take a look at this survey...
I've never done a survey talk filled with our own episodes before, so it was a first for me too, and I really felt that our talk would be over in a flash.
I said it with all the energy I could muster, but I didn't expect it to be so long.
I had prepared many other sections for each one, you know, I had a February-like project prepared, but we didn't end up doing it.
But we didn't end up doing any of them.
Can I do one project?
There was one project that they really wanted me to do.
It was a Valentine's Day project called "Shiritori for Otome in Love" (Shiritori for Otome in Love).
Heart-rending? Know the lines that a girl in love would say.
Let's take one turn at a time.
The two members who are the least suitable for this project are...
The two who haven't had much experience with the game until now.
Shiritori no Surprise?
They're making up the roles.
A-A-A-3.
Linda, Linda, Linda.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
Dom rat?
Like a domme rat.
Beautiful.
I want to be beautiful.
Like a dominatrix?
The picture doesn't do it justice.
I'd like to comment back. I want to comment back to you.
Like, "You're making me melt.
And then there was someone who was expecting me to say something like, "That's Tolga-chan," but now I'm like, "Really?
But now it's "Rinri nanda nada".
But, but, but, but... what does "but" mean?
It's not good at all. It's hard. I really don't care.
What should I do? I'm afraid of this time.
I know... a girl in love... that's what I'm going to say...
I don't want to say it.
No, but I don't want to say it
I just thought of something that's probably the right thing to say.
It just popped into your head? That's what you're saying.
I have to say it.
If it came to you...
If it comes to mind...
Okay, then, everyone, it's really Valentine's Day.
I'll put it out.
Do you like it?
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching.